<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ransomware.live RSS Feed</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/rss.xml</link><description>Last 50 entries monitoring by Ransomware.live</description><image><url>https://www.ransomware.live/ransomwarelive.png</url><title>Ransomware.live RSS Feed</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/rss.xml</link></image><item><title>🏴‍☠️ play has just published a now post : InPro electric</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play</link><description>Germany</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play?eb5f2f38-b478-11ed-b308-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 19:23:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : Schwartz Hautmont Port Shop</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description>Schwartz Hautmont is a private Spanish corporation established in 1963 in Tarragona, South of Barcelona, Spain. The company is in the steel construction business, offering a wide range of products and related services</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?eb5f4a01-b478-11ed-8393-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 15:12:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : The Keen Group</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>A little about us - The Keen Group provides a professional, licensed, hassle-free minicab &amp; courier service across south London</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?eb5f4bd0-b478-11ed-afd6-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 11:21:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Glovers Solicitors LLP</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Glovers was founded as Glover &amp; Co in Mayfair in 1932 by Sir Gerald Glover, a prominent and respected Central London property developer and solicitor.  We have since grown to become a modern and highly regarded, property-focused legal practice and are now based in Covent Garden.  Glovers is recognised by clients and independent legal directories as a genuinely partner-led law firm, with in- depth strengths in its chosen practice areas.  Our clients value not only our legal expertise, but also our dedicated work ethic and the commercial approach that we bring to negotiations and problem solving. We are, as a result, retained by a wide range of businesses – from well known restaurant and retail brands and major construction companies to specialist banks and lending institutions.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?eb5f4cef-b478-11ed-9540-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 11:16:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ ransomhouse has just published a now post : AESCULAPIUS Farmaceutici</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/ransomhouse</link><description>The Research and Development Division is the heart of the company, which invests significant resources in innovation to develop new pharmaceutical products and new formulations with high technological content.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/ransomhouse?eb5f4df0-b478-11ed-bc2b-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 07:17:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ mallox has just published a now post : "FICCI"</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/mallox</link><description>Established in 1927, FICCI is the largest and oldest apex business organisation in India. Its history is closely interwoven with India's struggle for independence, its industrialization, and its emergence as one of the most rapidly growing global economies.A non-government, not-for-profit organisation, FICCI is the voice of India's business and industry. From influencing policy to encouraging debate, engaging with policy makers and civil society, FICCI articulates the views and concerns of industry. It serves its members from the Indian private and public corporate sectors and multinational companies, drawing its strength from diverse regional chambers of commerce and industry across states, reaching out to over 2,50,000 companies.FICCI provides a platform for networking and consensus building within and across sectors and is the first port of call for Indian industry, policy makers and the international business community.  FILES: https://anonfiles.com/h9F2u9Z3yc/FICCI_rar PASSWORD: BUHgv97yt9f7fcv7c-p8 </description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/mallox?eb5f4edc-b478-11ed-8659-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 07:16:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Empresa Distribuidora de Electricidad del Este, Revenue $633.6M</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Overview: Edeeste is an electricity distribution company. It offers commercial, industrial and business development, installment agreement, power change, circuit and supply status, concurrence consultation, net measurement program, and other services. --- Industries: Appliances, Electrical, and Electronics Manufacturing --- Type: Government Agency Private --- Company size: 1,001-5,000 employees --- Website: http://www.edeeste.com.do --- Locations: Santo Domingo Este, Santo Domingo HQ Dominican Republic Av. San Vicente de Paúl 321 --- Revenue: $633.6M ---------</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?eb5f4fc4-b478-11ed-a553-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 05:29:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : Stone and Electrical Contractors</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description>Stone &amp; Sons Electrical Contractors, Inc offers a wide range of electrical services in the Transportation, Industrial and Municipal Markets including new construction, custom designs/installations, repairs, maintenance and systems upgrades.﻿First established in 1994, our business now has more than 85 field employees as well as a large support staff. Our support staff includes a team of project managers, estimators, and electrical engineers. Together, our team offers our clients over 160 years of combined experience.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?eb5f509e-b478-11ed-a79c-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 23:14:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ ransomhouse has just published a now post : Bond It</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/ransomhouse</link><description>For almost two decades, Bond It has been a manufacturer of high performance, high quality building chemicals such as sealants, adhesives, grouts, cleaners, expanding foams, fillers, decorating sundries, landscaping products and other similar products.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/ransomhouse?eb5f5189-b478-11ed-acf6-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 23:13:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : PRESTIGE MAINTENANCE USA WAS HACKED</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Who is Prestige Maintenance USA  Prestige Maintenance USA, established in 1976 and headquartered in Plano, Texas, provides janitorial services that offer contract and project cleaning, general maintenance, window washing, carpet care, sanitation, and recycling services  Headquarters: 1808 10th St Ste 300, Plano, Texas, 75074, United States Phone Number: (972) 578-9801 Revenue: $472.4M Linkedin: http://www.linkedin.com/company/prestige-maintenance-usa Facebook: http://www.facebook.com/pmusa76 Twitter: http://www.twitter.com/prestige_m_usa</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?eb5f5269-b478-11ed-b46d-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 23:13:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Kendall Hunt Publishing</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Founded in 1944, Kendall Hunt Publishing is a publisher of hands-on, inquiry-based science, mathematics, and gifted curricula for grades PreK-12. Their research and standards-based programs are available in both print and digital components that encompass students</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?eb5f5344-b478-11ed-ad3e-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 23:11:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ medusa has just published a now post : Moose, Martin, Haynes &amp; Lundy</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa</link><description>For years, Moose, Martin, Haynes &amp; Lundy, P.A. has been providing quality, personalized financial guidance to local individuals and businesses. Our expertise ranges from basic tax management and accounting services to more in-depth services such as audits, financia</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa?eb5f5424-b478-11ed-800c-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 21:14:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ ransomexx has just published a now post : BULOG</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/ransomexx</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/ransomexx?eb5f5523-b478-11ed-ab45-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 19:39:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ ragnarlocker has just published a now post : AASP claim there was no data leakage!</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/ragnarlocker</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/ragnarlocker?eb5f5618-b478-11ed-893a-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 19:38:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ medusa has just published a now post : RAYAB Consulting Engineers</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa</link><description>RAYAB Consulting Engineers Company was founded in 1984. Taking advantage of hundreds of experienced experts’ cooperation , know – how and scientific experiences, the company has studied , designed and supervised, water and water transmission infrastructural projects, consulting and studying services for potable, agricultural and industrial water consumption, urban and industrial water distribution and wastewater collecting and disposal networks, water and wastewater treatment plants, environmental and health services and water resources conservation as large and small projects throughout Iran In addition to offices in Tehran, it has offices in Isfahan , Ghazvin, Takestan, Gorgan, Karaj, Ghom, Kashan, Delijan, Malayer , Ilaam , Ahwaz, Dezful, Babolsar, Bojnourd, Mashhad, Esfarayen, Kashmar, Birjand, Bandarabbas, Sirjan and Sare – Pole – Zahab</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa?eb5f56f7-b478-11ed-9e90-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 19:37:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : ziapueblo.org</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>The Pueblo of Zia has operated a contemporary court since 2007. It is a court of general jurisdiction and oversees criminal and civil hearings. Currently the Court staff consists of a Chief Judge (part-time), a court clerk and a part time probation o...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?eb5f57d4-b478-11ed-97d4-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 19:25:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : nougat-carlier.be</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>For more than half a century, Carlier, a family business, has been making nougat by using the highest quality ingredients, in a wide variety of flavours. It all began in 1949: following the example of his father, a retail confectioner, Rodolphe Carli...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?eb5f58be-b478-11ed-b26b-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 15:26:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : siqueiracastro.com.br</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>stolen 470gb data - finance, acc, reports, contractsActing on all fronts of the business, the so-called full service , is what is expected of a contemporary law firm. We, at SiqueiraCastro, go further. We are pioneers in full solution . With high...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?eb5f5991-b478-11ed-b1a7-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 15:13:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : skylinetrisource.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Find the right fit for your brand with Skyline Trisource Exhibits and Environments in Cleveland. We create custom exhibits, without the custom price tag. Our high-impact graphics, modular structures and comprehensive services make great exhibit desig...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?eb5f5a5e-b478-11ed-9846-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 13:48:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : fosterfarms.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Change the negotiator.He's obstructing the deal and denying the facts and the obvious obvious. And doesn't want to use valid insurance!Here are scans of insurance documents from the network of companies:http://lockbitfile2tcudkcqqt2ve6btssyvqwl...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?eb5f5b29-b478-11ed-9f61-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 13:37:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : La Filipina</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>La Filipina Group of Companies (the "Company") is committed to ensure that its business is conducted, in all respects and all the times, according to rigorous ethical, professional and legal standards, which prevail from time to time, in the industrial sectors.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?eb5f5bf2-b478-11ed-9f1a-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 13:37:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Markas</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Sice 1985, Markas has been synonymous with high quality, innovative facility services. The founder, Mario Kasslatter, has successfully established a wide range of services in order to provide each customer with a tailor-made facility servicesn.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?eb5f5cba-b478-11ed-8999-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 13:37:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Summit Brands</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Summit Brands is a family-owned business started in 1958 and offers highly effective, sustainable, and innovative household cleaning products</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?eb5f5d83-b478-11ed-a579-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 13:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : FUTURE BUILDINGS WAS HACKED. MORE THAN 150GB SENSETIVE DATA LEAKED</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Who is Future Buildings  Future Buildings is a family owned and operated company that takes pride in providing customers with steel buildings  Home Improvement &amp; Hardware Retail · Canada · 132 Employees   Headquarters: 1405 Denison St, Markham, Ontario, L3R 5V2, Canada Phone Number: (800) 668-5111 Revenue: $27.2M Linkedin: http://www.linkedin.com/company/future-buildings Facebook: http://www.facebook.com/futuresteelbuildings Twitter: http://www.twitter.com/futuresteel</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?eb5f5e6a-b478-11ed-bfd4-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 13:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : City of Lakewood</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Lakewood is a city in Pierce County, Washington, United States. The population was 63,612 at the 2020 census.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?eb5f5f2f-b478-11ed-8ae0-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 13:37:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : EncinoEnergy</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Encino Energy is one of the largest private natural gas and oil producers in the U.S. and a top 25 North American natural gas producer. While headquartered in Houston, our operations in the prolific Northern Utica Shale make us the largest oil producer in Ohio and the second-largest natural gas producer in the state.  But beyond our day-to-day operations, we are a company dedicated to our values of results, transparency, innovation, ownership, and sustainability. These foundational values guide our employees and make us who we are. Encino Energy’s proven management team is deeply committed to our people, and we are fully invested in the communities we call home.  Encino Energy is committed to doing the right things for the right reasons while never losing sight of safety and sustainability. We focus on the long-term, which means sustainable, safe, and environmentally conscious operations, and carefully managed risks.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?eb5f5ff5-b478-11ed-abd5-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 13:35:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : kboattorneys.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Organizations, groups of attorneys, and others across the country have recognized KBA’s attorneys in many different ways. Our attorneys are published and are invited to speak at conferences where thousands of attorneys from across America come to lea...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?eb5f60ba-b478-11ed-856e-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 23:24:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : treves-group.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Trèves est un groupe industriel spécialisé dans la fourniture d'équipements pour l'industrie automobile.250 GB DATAexample creds ESXIhttps://10.230.1.11/ui/ root:oel28&amp;CPhttps://10.230.1.21/ui/ root:oel28&amp;CPhttps://10.230.1.15/ui/ root:oel2...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?eb5f6182-b478-11ed-bcde-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 23:24:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : beacontech.net</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Since 1999 Beacon Technologies has been a leading partner in the transformation of the Nashville landscape through an integrated process of delivering Telecom, Audio Visual and Life and Safety expertise to the design and development of leading edge c...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?eb5f624a-b478-11ed-98c5-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 23:24:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : vuu.edu</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Virginia Union UniversityVirginia Union University is a private historically black Baptist university in Richmond, Virginia. It is affiliated with the American Baptist Churches USA.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?eb5f6316-b478-11ed-876c-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 23:12:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : lasegunda.com.ar</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>La Segunda Seguros CLSG is a company that operates in the Insurance industry. It employs 2,001-5,000 people and has $500M-$1B of revenue. The company is headquartered in Rosario, Santa Fe Province, ArgentinaDuring our attack, all the servers of t...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?eb5f640b-b478-11ed-afd2-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:28:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : lyonhealy.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>From the hallowed halls of the New York Philharmonic to the Bolshoi Ballet, Lyon &amp; Healy Harps is acclaimed throughout the world for its remarkable depth and clarity of sound, breathtaking designs, and rich heritage of quality craftsmanship. With 130...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?eb5f64e4-b478-11ed-be3b-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:16:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ vendetta has just published a now post : Highwealth</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vendetta</link><description>In the best location, build the best house, the best homeMore than 30 years ago, we started our business in Kaohsiung. After laying the foundation, we developed all the way north and expanded to Tainan, Taichung, Hsinchu, Taipei, New...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vendetta?eb5f65ba-b478-11ed-9907-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 15:13:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ play has just published a now post : I???o e???t???</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play</link><description>Germany</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play?eb5f668e-b478-11ed-b92e-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 02:44:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lorenz has just published a now post : Hopsteiner</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lorenz</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lorenz?eb5f676a-b478-11ed-b7bb-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 17:25:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : UNIS</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description>Founded in 1989, Unis LLC has grown into a majority, nationally recognized Third-Party Logistics Provider (3PL). From humble beginnings with just a few trucks operating in Southern California, Unis has expanded into all major US markets, impacting the successful flow of commerce with superior technology, smarter supply chains, and faster execution.We credit our growth to an agile, customer-driven mindset, and strategic investments in technologies that give our clients the visibility and operational insights they require in today’s dynamic supply chain environment</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?eb5f685e-b478-11ed-89a7-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 15:13:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : DALLAS SCHOOL DISTRICT</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description>Dallas School District is centered on students, powered by collaboration, built on equity and driven by excellence.Headquarters: 111 SW Ash St, Dallas, Oregon, 97338, United StatesPhone: (503) 623-5594</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?eb5f6934-b478-11ed-81c9-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 13:33:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : Ancora - Sistemas de Fixacao</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?eb5f6a31-b478-11ed-984f-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 13:32:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ qilin has just published a now post : https://https://gigatron.rs/</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/qilin</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/qilin?eb5f6b22-b478-11ed-8a7b-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 13:30:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : carlocksystems.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Car Lock Systems is dé leverancier van autosleutels en autosloten voor automotive bedrijven.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?eb5f6bf5-b478-11ed-8e89-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 09:23:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ medusa has just published a now post : International Center of Photography</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa</link><description>New York,  374 Employees. 

The International Center of Photography is the world's leading institution dedicated to photography and visual culture. Cornell Capa founded ICP in 1974 to champion "concerned photography"-socially and politically minded images that can educate and change the world</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa?eb5f6cc7-b478-11ed-9550-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 23:14:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : BakerMechanicalInc.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Baker Mechanical Inc. is a family-oriented company that prides itself on ensuring unsurpassed customer satisfaction.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?eb5f6dab-b478-11ed-8c20-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 19:44:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : jetboxcargo.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>El Corporativo JetBox como especialista en el servicio de logística internacional, posee una amplia trayectoria en transporte aéreo y marítimo,con origen en Estados Unidos para Costa Rica. Cuenta con su propia Agencia Aduanal y ofrece los servicios...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?eb5f6e7e-b478-11ed-b53f-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 19:44:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : servicesfinanciersjdf.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>JDF Services financiers est un cabinet d'assurances collectives et de personnes spécialisé dans le domaine depuis le début des années 90.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?eb5f6f4a-b478-11ed-b69c-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 19:44:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : laremo.de</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Laremo Ihr Spezialist für Landtechnik, Nutzfahrzeuge, Baumaschinen, Fahrzeug- und Umwelttechnik, Stahlbau, Reifencenter, Traktoren, Mähdrescher, CLAAS, IVECO in Thüringen Greiz, Gera, Jena, Erfurt.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?eb5f7016-b478-11ed-a55c-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 19:43:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : elliotthomes.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Find your new construction home by Elliott Homes, home builder in Sacramento CA, Phoenix AZ and Yuma AZ. Explore our new home communities today!</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?eb5f710b-b478-11ed-a287-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 19:39:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : anthonymartin.be</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Anthony Martin encourage une consommation responsable de ses bières. En entrant dans ce site vous reconnaissez avoir l'âge légal pour boire de l'alcoo</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?eb5f71e3-b478-11ed-a065-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 19:26:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Leal Group</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>The Leal Group is a diverse group of companies contributing to the economic development of Mauritius.During the last nine decades, the Leal Group has expanded into a wide range of industries including medical, consumer goods, automotive, information technology, engineering and tourism. The Leal Group is headquartered in Moka, Mauritius.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?eb5f72cb-b478-11ed-89ad-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 19:24:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : AMADA WELD TECH</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Based in Southern California, AMADA WELD TECH Inc. is a leading manufacturer of equipment and systems for resistance welding, laser welding, laser marking, laser cutting, laser micromachining, and hot bar bonding. Visit our Virtual Showroom!  The company provides products to a wide range of markets, including the medical device, battery, electric vehicle and solar industries, as well as the global electronics, automotive and general industrial markets.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?eb5f739d-b478-11ed-8ffb-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 19:24:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Hengmei Optoelectronics Co.,Ltd.</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Hengmei Optoelectronics Co., Ltd. was established in May 2014, located in Kunshan Development Zone, Jiangsu Province, with a registered capital of 3.25278 billion yuan. At present, four production bases in Kunshan, Fuzhou, Hefei and Danyang have been established and planned, and the total annual production capacity of polarizers is planned to be 220 million square meters. It will become the world's leading polarizer manufacturer and provide high-quality panel factories in many countries and regions around the world. , Stable polarizer supply. Among them, Hengmei Kunshan factory has a total of two polarizer production lines. Line 1 has a width of 1.5M. It was officially mass-produced in January 2017, with a monthly production capacity of 1.8 million square meters. Line 2 has a width of 2.5M and began mass production in September 2019. , with a monthly production capacity of 3.2 million square meters. The two lines have achieved an annual production capacity of 60 million square meters. Hengmei Fuzhou factory has newly added two 2.6M ultra-wide polarizer production lines. It is planned to start mass production in Q4 of 2022. After full production, the two lines will have an annual production capacity of 90 million square meters.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?eb5f7470-b478-11ed-8aaa-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 19:24:48 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>