<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ransomware.live RSS Feed</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/rss.xml</link><description>Last 50 entries monitoring by Ransomware.live</description><image><url>https://www.ransomware.live/ransomwarelive.png</url><title>Ransomware.live RSS Feed</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/rss.xml</link></image><item><title>🏴‍☠️ medusa has just published a now post : Garbarino SAICeI</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa</link><description>Garbarino, headquartered in Argentina, founded in 1951, is a retail company offering a wide range of products, including technology, appliances, furniture, sportswear, tools. Garbarino offers the most prestigious brands with over 5000 items.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa?1a08590f-becf-11ed-b07e-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 23:06:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ medusa has just published a now post : National Business Furniture</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa</link><description>National Business Furniture (NBF), founded in 1975, is an office furniture manufacturer headquartered in Milwaukee, Wisconsin. The company has additional offices in New York, Chicago, Los Angeles, Atlanta, Dallas, Phoenix and Seattle. In 2006, NBF was acquired by TAKKT AG, a leading direct marketing specialist for B2B business equipment in Europe and North America.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa?1a087054-becf-11ed-a8de-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 23:06:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : pmsoffice.de</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>The hotel software hotline is the award-winning hotel program for small and large hotels, with individual extensions and TSE certification.Data related hotline software and hotels they cooperate.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?1a0871ea-becf-11ed-a0bc-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 23:05:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : delawarelife.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Delaware Life Insurance Company is a leading provider of annuity and life insurance products in the United States. The company was established in connection with the purchase by Delaware Life Holdings, LLC of the domestic U.S. annuity business and ce...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?1a087342-becf-11ed-84a4-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 21:01:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : Wellington Power Corporation</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description>At Wellington Power, success is based upon diversified excellence in electrical construction, automated metering infrastructure, telecommunications, and general construction services for utility, industrial, and public sector clients. The company has been developed to handle projects ranging from simple service calls to multimillion dollar installations.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?1a087452-becf-11ed-8326-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 19:07:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ blackbyte has just published a now post : Falcon Holdings</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbyte</link><description>Falcon created the management company of professionals to provide operational expertise and administrative services to a wide range of companies. It serves clients with a level of commitment that is first class in the industry. Implementation of many programs in the company are designed to promote a diverse work force and helping employees excel. Khan is a true example of someone who has taken advantage of the opportunities available and created value to the clients, employees and investors.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbyte?1a087546-becf-11ed-a2c4-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 19:06:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : Walker SCM</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description>Walker SCM, LLC provides Global Supply Chain Services ranging from Transportation (Air and Ocean Freight Forwarding) to Warehousing Solutions that also include specialized value added services. We have stolen from their network 20GB in total, including: HR;Work files;Finance;Clients and others.Feel free to check!Archive password: 4+"JdvDyH[a4:o@9D,b$wy!'~W]~jrk/z_"yiz&lt;r</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?1a087633-becf-11ed-a6c1-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 17:11:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : Brauerei Schimpf</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description>Headquarters: 1 Hauptstraße, Neustetten, Baden-Wuerttemberg, 72149, GermanyPhone Number: +49 747298940</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?1a087716-becf-11ed-9a1f-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 11:06:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : Thomaston Mills</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description>Thomaston Mills was founded in 1899 by R.E. Hightower and is the oldest domestic sheet mill in the USA. We were owned by the Hightower family until 2001, and have been owned by the Zaslow family since that time. Combined the two families have over 200 years of textile experience. Thomaston Mills continues to operate as a family business that puts the customer first.We currently specialize in manufacturing and distribution of the highest quality bed and bath linens to the hospitality, healthcare and institutional markets. We finish millions of yards of fabric each year at our bleachery in Easley, South Carolina and cut and sew this fabric in our 250,000 square foot manufacturing and warehousing facility located in Thomaston, GA.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?1a08780f-becf-11ed-a628-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 09:05:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : audio-technica.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Audio-Technica was founded in Japan on 17th April 1962 by Hideo Matsushita. After operating from a small flat above a ramen shop in Shinjuku, Audio-Technica opened a larger headquarters in Machida, Tokyo, where the company still operates today.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?1a0878f2-becf-11ed-a727-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Mar 2023 07:08:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : The WorkPlace</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description>The WorkPlace was originally incorporated as the Private Industry Council of Southern Connecticut on August 11, 1983. Today, we conduct comprehensive planning, and coordinate regional and state-wide workforce development programs to prepare people for careers while strengthening the workforce for employers.We do this chiefly by administering workforce development funds and coordinating providers of job training and education programs. But our role is actually much larger. We believe in the power of ideas to affect great change – so we act as convener, catalyst, collaborator and advocate for workforce development throughout the region, state and nation.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?1a0879d3-becf-11ed-a790-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 19:10:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ blackbyte has just published a now post : Wagner CAT</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbyte</link><description>Since 1976, Wagner has been selling and renting quality Cat machines used in heavy construction, building construction, mining, waste handling, paving, municipal and governmental applications, forestry and more.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbyte?1a087adf-becf-11ed-8a22-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 03:37:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ monti has just published a now post : Regional Transportation Authority</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/monti</link><description>A government agency created by the State of Illinois to coordinate the Chicago region’s transit system https://rtachicago.org</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/monti?1a087bc5-becf-11ed-8fc4-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 19:12:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ clop has just published a now post : GROUPAMANA.COM</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop?1a087ca5-becf-11ed-93a0-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 19:11:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ medusa has just published a now post : Minneapolis Public Schools</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa</link><description>Minneapolis Public Schools (MPS) or Special School District Number 1 is a public school district serving students in pre-kindergarten through twelfth grade from Minneapolis, Minnesota. Minneapolis Public Schools enrolls 36,370 students in public primary and secondary schools. The district administers about one hundred public schools including forty-five elementary schools, seven middle schools, seven high schools, eight special education schools, eight alternative schools, nineteen contract alternative schools, and five charter schools. With authority granted by the state legislature, the school board makes policy, selects the superintendent, and oversees the district's budget, curriculum, personnel, and facilities. Students speak ninety different languages at home and most school communications are printed in English, Hmong, Spanish, and Somali.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa?1a087d97-becf-11ed-81d4-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 09:17:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : Krinos Foods</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description>Krinos Foods LLC is one of the largest importers and manufacturers of specialty foods in North America. Krinos imports over 3,000 frozen, refrigerated and dry food products from over 25 countries. These products include cheeses, olives, olive oils, pasta and etc.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?1a087e76-becf-11ed-8b37-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 17:15:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : Wilhelm</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description>Egmont Wilhelm GmbHWilly-Messerschmitt-Straße 1473457 EssingenDeutschland</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?1a087f51-becf-11ed-9596-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 17:15:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : PROTEKTOR</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description>The Protektor brand of profiles for plaster, render and drywall has been established for over 100 years. The first to introduce the manufacture of plaster bead and drywall steel profiles for partitions and ceiling constructions in Europe we have continued to develop and innovation solutions to meet the needs of system partners and the construction industry alike.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?1a08802b-becf-11ed-a853-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 17:15:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ mallox has just published a now post : Circa Jewels</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/mallox</link><description>Circa Jewels is the leading international buyer of pre-owned fine jewelry, diamonds and watches. If Circa Jewels fail to take responsibility for their security weakness, all of their and their clients' confidential will be published.  File Tree - https://anonfiles.com/N52cufc5z0/filetree_txt Last date - 20th March 2023 Contact ( https://tox.chat ) - AE3750EE1BE48D86104E6FB1DADC32469A31242EFC205A3EC47EF7689E3F103472A4DBFFF399 </description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/mallox?1a088152-becf-11ed-af02-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 13:24:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ vicesociety has just published a now post : Kventa Kft</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety</link><description>Our company's main field of activity has been the trade of computing devices since the beginning. Today, our offer ranges from the installation of local networks and professional computer technology devices, through PC components to computer technology accessories, resulting in a range of several thousand products.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety?1a088245-becf-11ed-832b-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 09:23:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ medusa has just published a now post : The Institute of Space Technology</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa</link><description>The Institute of Space Technology (also known as IST) is a public university located in Islamabad, Pakistan. IST space program aims at designing, building, launching and succesfully operating the Pico-Satellite standard CubeSat. The program is led by Communication Systems Engineering (CSE). Established in 2002 under the auspices of the Pakistan National Space Agency. IST offers a wide array of undergraduate and graduate degrees in partnership of Beihang University and University of Surrey.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa?1a088321-becf-11ed-bdc0-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 09:23:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ clop has just published a now post : HATCHBANK.COM</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop?1a0883fc-becf-11ed-b2f3-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 09:21:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Lehigh Valley Health Network</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Founded in 1899, Lehigh Valley Health Network is a healthcare network based in Allentown, Pennsylvania. The healthcare network serves Pennsylvania and its flagship hospital is Lehigh Valley Hospital.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?1a0884d8-becf-11ed-967a-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 02:46:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Los Altos Foods</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>We have downloaded 1TB of your data, including full dump of customers attached below. If you will keep silence we will publish whole data pack.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?1a0885c2-becf-11ed-b902-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 02:44:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ vicesociety has just published a now post : HAW Hamburg</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety</link><description>Developing sustainable solutions to the societal challenges of today and tomorrow. This is the goal of the Hamburg University of Applied Sciences (HAW Hamburg), northern Germany's leading applied sciences university when it comes to reflective practice. People from more than 100 countries help make HAW Hamburg what it is, and our diversity is our particular strength.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety?1a08869c-becf-11ed-baa3-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 21:15:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ mallox has just published a now post : AddWeb Solution Pvt</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/mallox</link><description>AddWeb Solution Pvt is a leading offshore development company provides a one-stop website, mobile, cloud, and digital marketing solution. If AddWeb Solution Pvt  fail to take responsibility for their security weakness,  all of their and their clients' confidential will be published.  File Tree - https://anonfiles.com/gab0ifc8z3/filetree_txt Last date - 19th March 2023 Contact ( https://tox.chat ) - AE3750EE1BE48D86104E6FB1DADC32469A31242EFC205A3EC47EF7689E3F103472A4DBFFF399 </description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/mallox?1a08878b-becf-11ed-bdd3-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 13:29:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ bianlian has just published a now post : P* ***** **** L****** ***</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian</link><description>Indonesian company that operates in agricultural industry.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian?1a08887b-becf-11ed-99fc-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 09:14:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ bianlian has just published a now post : R****</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian</link><description>A manufacturer of wheels and rims from Canada.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian?1a08896d-becf-11ed-9ceb-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 09:14:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ bianlian has just published a now post : V******* ****</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian</link><description>European real estate company.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian?1a088a4a-becf-11ed-b276-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 09:14:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ bianlian has just published a now post : A***** ********* **********</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian</link><description>Furniture company located in USA.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian?1a088b24-becf-11ed-9b8c-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 09:14:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ bianlian has just published a now post : S***** ***********</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian</link><description>Dental clinic located in USA.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian?1a088bfd-becf-11ed-ac31-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 09:14:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ bianlian has just published a now post : S*********** **********</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian</link><description>USA educational organization.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian?1a088cdb-becf-11ed-92df-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 09:14:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ bianlian has just published a now post : T******** ***** **********</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian</link><description>USA educational organization.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian?1a088db7-becf-11ed-b366-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 09:14:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ mallox has just published a now post : AICHELIN UNITHERM</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/mallox</link><description>Two leading manufacturers of heat treatment furnaces Unitherm Engineers Limited (India) and Aichelin Holding GmbH (Austria) formed a new 50:50 Joint Venture Company (JVC) in India in 2010. The newly incorporated JVC Aichelin Unitherm Heat Treatment Systems India Private Limited is headquartered in Talegaon, Pune (Maharashtra).Whatever part you play in the field of industrial heat treatment, AICHELIN UNITHERM has a solution for you. As diverse as the product portfolio may be, certain things apply to every solution: reliability and economic efficiency. AICHELIN UNITHERM in joint venture with AICHELIN Group offers extensive experience and skill guaranteeing the security of a stable and strong group, as your partners and service providers.Industrial heat treatment of metallic parts and components is our skill and passion. AICHELIN UNITHERM is the leading manufacturer of Industrial Heat Treatment Plants technology and services in India.   DATA: https://anonfiles.com/D583Qcb3z9/AICHELIN_UNITHERM_rar PASSWORD:  n246nm245&amp;TC675tcd^R </description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/mallox?1a088ea6-becf-11ed-b69f-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 13:31:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Traffic Ticket Office</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Since 1993, the Traffic Ticket Office, has successfully been serving clients in Miami and South Florida with their civil and criminal traffic violations. Hundreds of thousands of cases have been handled by our experienced and reputable attorneys. We are able to offer our clients the benefits of saving time and money, preserving their driving rights and preventing the accumulation of points on their records. Most often, we have managed to do this without requiring a personal court appearance by the client.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?1a088f81-becf-11ed-9ddf-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 09:14:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : SkyFiber Networks</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>SkyFiber Internet is leading the way in hybrid fiber and fixed wireless internet service by giving our customers the most reliable, fastest Internet connection out there.  We look forward to providing you with the best Internet available. No one loves building networks more than we do.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?1a089057-becf-11ed-b7ec-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 09:14:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : CMMG Inc</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>MMG ® was established in 2002, when John, Jeff, Gretchen, and Stephanie Overstreet made the decision to create a quality AR rifle that can be afforded by everyone. Since that time, things have continued to get better and better. Although the nature of our business continues to evolve, one thing does not—our commitment to meet each and every morning to pray for God’s wisdom in managing the enormous responsibility that comes with this business. By His grace, we have grown every year! CMMG is constantly looking for new ways to improve our products, processes and company at large. Both our customer service and product lineup continue to be second to none, and all of our rifles and firearms parts are made in the United States from the best materials available. CMMG guarantees its products against defects in material or workmanship for the life of the product. CMMG Inc. will repair, replace or substitute any product(s) if a defect in material or workmanship is found.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?1a089133-becf-11ed-9110-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 09:14:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Welty Building Company</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>1.5TB including full clients info, confidential building drawings, engineering information "Build to Last" now public.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?1a08920d-becf-11ed-bc50-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 09:14:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : blackswanhealth</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Announcement Data Leakage of company www.blackswanhealth.com.au</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?1a0892e7-becf-11ed-9f87-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 09:11:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ vicesociety has just published a now post : HUNOSA</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety</link><description>We are a business group that transforms, like energy. After decades as a benchmark in a strategic sector such as coal, we have become a company focused on energy, energy services and the environment.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety?1a0893da-becf-11ed-9926-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 23:13:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ ragnarlocker has just published a now post : New Leak in lawyers company AASP.</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/ragnarlocker</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/ragnarlocker?1a0894e1-becf-11ed-80e4-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 19:19:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ ragnarlocker has just published a now post : New Leak in lawyers company.</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/ragnarlocker</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/ragnarlocker?1a0895ca-becf-11ed-860a-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 17:19:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ bianlian has just published a now post : ACCSC</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian</link><description>Accrediting Commission Of Career Schools Colleges. ACCSC’s scope of recognition with the U.S. Department of Education includes the accreditation of postsecondary, non-degree-granting institutions and degree-granting institutions that are predominantly organized to educate students for occupational, trade and technical careers.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian?1a0896cd-becf-11ed-8db2-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 17:18:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ bianlian has just published a now post : Zerbe Retirement Community</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian</link><description>Zerbe Retirement Community is part of the Hospitals &amp; Physicians Clinics industry.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian?1a0897ad-becf-11ed-acd3-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 17:18:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ bianlian has just published a now post : PLP Architecture</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian</link><description>PLP Architecture is part of the Architecture, Engineering &amp; Design industry.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian?1a089885-becf-11ed-ba88-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 17:18:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ bianlian has just published a now post : M**** M************</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian</link><description>The Company custom fabrication of shell and tube heat exchangers, ASME pressure vessels, columns, and tanks for a variety of processing industries.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian?1a089960-becf-11ed-9d9b-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 17:18:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ bianlian has just published a now post : Parques Reunidos</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian</link><description>Parques Reunidos is an international entertainment operator based in Madrid, Spain. The group operates over 60 parks in about dozen countries. Parques Reunidos operates theme and amusement parks, zoos, water parks, family entertainment centers, and cable cars.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian?1a089a39-becf-11ed-a2a9-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 17:18:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ play has just published a now post : Oakland</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play</link><description>United States</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play?1a089b26-becf-11ed-91b2-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 05:42:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : FIMM</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description>Industry: Chemicals and allied products, nec</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?1a089c04-becf-11ed-b7be-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 19:23:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ ransomexx has just published a now post : Bettuzzi And Partners</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/ransomexx</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/ransomexx?1a089cf2-becf-11ed-bee3-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 09:21:01 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>