<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ransomware.live RSS Feed</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/rss.xml</link><description>Last 50 entries monitoring by Ransomware.live</description><image><url>https://www.ransomware.live/ransomwarelive.png</url><title>Ransomware.live RSS Feed</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/rss.xml</link></image><item><title>🏴‍☠️ mallox has just published a now post : AICHELIN UNITHERM</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/mallox</link><description>Two leading manufacturers of heat treatment furnaces Unitherm Engineers Limited (India) and Aichelin Holding GmbH (Austria) formed a new 50:50 Joint Venture Company (JVC) in India in 2010. The newly incorporated JVC Aichelin Unitherm Heat Treatment Systems India Private Limited is headquartered in Talegaon, Pune (Maharashtra).Whatever part you play in the field of industrial heat treatment, AICHELIN UNITHERM has a solution for you. As diverse as the product portfolio may be, certain things apply to every solution: reliability and economic efficiency. AICHELIN UNITHERM in joint venture with AICHELIN Group offers extensive experience and skill guaranteeing the security of a stable and strong group, as your partners and service providers.Industrial heat treatment of metallic parts and components is our skill and passion. AICHELIN UNITHERM is the leading manufacturer of Industrial Heat Treatment Plants technology and services in India.   DATA: https://anonfiles.com/D583Qcb3z9/AICHELIN_UNITHERM_rar PASSWORD:  n246nm245&amp;TC675tcd^R </description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/mallox?6a383e2c-bab1-11ed-af32-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 13:31:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Traffic Ticket Office</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Since 1993, the Traffic Ticket Office, has successfully been serving clients in Miami and South Florida with their civil and criminal traffic violations. Hundreds of thousands of cases have been handled by our experienced and reputable attorneys. We are able to offer our clients the benefits of saving time and money, preserving their driving rights and preventing the accumulation of points on their records. Most often, we have managed to do this without requiring a personal court appearance by the client.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?6a38592c-bab1-11ed-adb6-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 09:14:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : SkyFiber Networks</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>SkyFiber Internet is leading the way in hybrid fiber and fixed wireless internet service by giving our customers the most reliable, fastest Internet connection out there.  We look forward to providing you with the best Internet available. No one loves building networks more than we do.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?6a385aec-bab1-11ed-a6a5-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 09:14:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : CMMG Inc</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>MMG ® was established in 2002, when John, Jeff, Gretchen, and Stephanie Overstreet made the decision to create a quality AR rifle that can be afforded by everyone. Since that time, things have continued to get better and better. Although the nature of our business continues to evolve, one thing does not—our commitment to meet each and every morning to pray for God’s wisdom in managing the enormous responsibility that comes with this business. By His grace, we have grown every year! CMMG is constantly looking for new ways to improve our products, processes and company at large. Both our customer service and product lineup continue to be second to none, and all of our rifles and firearms parts are made in the United States from the best materials available. CMMG guarantees its products against defects in material or workmanship for the life of the product. CMMG Inc. will repair, replace or substitute any product(s) if a defect in material or workmanship is found.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?6a385c11-bab1-11ed-9c40-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 09:14:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Welty Building Company</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>1.5TB including full clients info, confidential building drawings, engineering information "Build to Last" now public.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?6a385d34-bab1-11ed-9ac6-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 09:14:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : blackswanhealth</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Announcement Data Leakage of company www.blackswanhealth.com.au</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?6a385e26-bab1-11ed-9867-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 04 Mar 2023 09:11:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ vicesociety has just published a now post : HUNOSA</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety</link><description>We are a business group that transforms, like energy. After decades as a benchmark in a strategic sector such as coal, we have become a company focused on energy, energy services and the environment.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety?6a385f16-bab1-11ed-b6fd-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 23:13:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ ragnarlocker has just published a now post : New Leak in lawyers company AASP.</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/ragnarlocker</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/ragnarlocker?6a386017-bab1-11ed-b844-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 19:19:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ ragnarlocker has just published a now post : New Leak in lawyers company.</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/ragnarlocker</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/ragnarlocker?6a3860f9-bab1-11ed-87dc-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 17:19:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ bianlian has just published a now post : ACCSC</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian</link><description>Accrediting Commission Of Career Schools Colleges. ACCSC’s scope of recognition with the U.S. Department of Education includes the accreditation of postsecondary, non-degree-granting institutions and degree-granting institutions that are predominantly organized to educate students for occupational, trade and technical careers.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian?6a3861d6-bab1-11ed-994b-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 17:18:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ bianlian has just published a now post : Zerbe Retirement Community</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian</link><description>Zerbe Retirement Community is part of the Hospitals &amp; Physicians Clinics industry.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian?6a3862b2-bab1-11ed-b320-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 17:18:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ bianlian has just published a now post : PLP Architecture</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian</link><description>PLP Architecture is part of the Architecture, Engineering &amp; Design industry.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian?6a3863a1-bab1-11ed-bc15-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 17:18:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ bianlian has just published a now post : M**** M************</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian</link><description>The Company custom fabrication of shell and tube heat exchangers, ASME pressure vessels, columns, and tanks for a variety of processing industries.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian?6a38647c-bab1-11ed-af9a-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 17:18:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ bianlian has just published a now post : Parques Reunidos</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian</link><description>Parques Reunidos is an international entertainment operator based in Madrid, Spain. The group operates over 60 parks in about dozen countries. Parques Reunidos operates theme and amusement parks, zoos, water parks, family entertainment centers, and cable cars.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian?6a38658f-bab1-11ed-961a-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 17:18:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ play has just published a now post : Oakland</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play</link><description>United States</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play?6a38666d-bab1-11ed-9ade-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 05:42:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : FIMM</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description>Industry: Chemicals and allied products, nec</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?6a386758-bab1-11ed-9dff-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 19:23:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ ransomexx has just published a now post : Bettuzzi And Partners</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/ransomexx</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/ransomexx?6a386839-bab1-11ed-97fb-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 09:21:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : ascentengrs.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?6a386911-bab1-11ed-b869-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 07:17:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ play has just published a now post : O???a??</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play</link><description>USA</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play?6a3869e7-bab1-11ed-94a5-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 02:45:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ snatch has just published a now post : The Metropolitan Opera</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/snatch</link><description>The Metropolitan Opera is a vibrant home for the most creative and talented singers, conductors, composers, musicians, stage directors, designers, visual artists, choreographers, and dancers from around the world.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/snatch?6a386abc-bab1-11ed-9116-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 23:14:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ ransomhouse has just published a now post : Audio Video</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/ransomhouse</link><description>Established in 1946 by WWII Veteran Milton A. Klarsfeld, Audio-Video Corporation was initially named The Albany Television Headquarters and was located on Hudson Avenue in Albany, NY. In 1954 the company changed its name to Audio-Video Corporation to better identify with current technology and services. Audio-Video Corporation headquarters is located in Albany, NY with a full service branch office in Syracuse, NY. Additionally, there are three satellite offices spread across NY and New England. Locations include Syracuse NY, Rochester NY, and Burlington VT.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/ransomhouse?6a386ba7-bab1-11ed-b004-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 17:23:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ ransomhouse has just published a now post : E&amp;S Heating &amp; Ventilation Ltd</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/ransomhouse</link><description>E&amp;S Heating &amp; Ventilation Ltd has been at the forefront of ductwork manufacturing technology and investment since 1972. We offer all forms of ductwork manufacture, galvanised, Flameshield fire rated and stainless steel, associated equipment selection along with procurement, installation, insulation, testing and commissioning for air handling systems.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/ransomhouse?6a386c84-bab1-11ed-a381-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 15:18:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ qilin has just published a now post : https://https://fsmsolicitors.co.uk/</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/qilin</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/qilin?6a386d73-bab1-11ed-b3bb-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 15:18:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ qilin has just published a now post : https://https://www.attentzorgenbehandeling.nl/</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/qilin</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/qilin?6a386e49-bab1-11ed-bbb0-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 15:16:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ vicesociety has just published a now post : Vesuvius</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety</link><description>Vesuvius provides engineering services and solutions principally to steel and foundry industries worldwide. With 17 research centres across the globe and an annual investment of 33.2 million in research and development, Vesuvius continues to lead innovation in our industry.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety?6a386f2f-bab1-11ed-81d8-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 11:10:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : tjel.net</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>AboutUs: Thai Jurong Engineering Limited (TJEL) was incorporated in December 1988. The company's core business is to provide engineering and construction services in the power generation sector. It also undertakes plant erection for industrial plant...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?6a387007-bab1-11ed-acf8-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 11:09:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ medusa has just published a now post : Kenya Airports Authority</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa</link><description>Kenya Airports Authority (KAA) is the owner and operator of nine civilian airports and airstrips in Kenya. Kenya Airports Authority was established by an act of Parliament in 1992, by the ruling Kenya African National Union government. The KAA Act, Cap 395, provides for the powers and functions of the Authority. Its head office is on the property of Jomo Kenyatta International Airport in Embakasi, Nairobi.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa?6a3870dc-bab1-11ed-a97c-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 09:13:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : hico-ics.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>HiCo-ICS has been a leading global provider of enterprise IT-solutions for industry, authorities and communities since 1997. HiCo-ICS provides process and system integration, information networking of technical logistic documentation and product info...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?6a3871c7-bab1-11ed-b39c-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 09:13:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : egas.no</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?6a3872a9-bab1-11ed-8bca-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 09:13:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Kimko Realty</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Kimco Realty® (NYSE:KIM) is a real estate investment trust (REIT) headquartered in Jericho, N.Y. that is North America’s largest publicly traded owner and operator of open-air, grocery-anchored shopping centers, and a growing portfolio of mixed-use assets. The company’s portfolio is primarily concentrated in the first-ring suburbs of the top major metropolitan markets, including those in high-barrier-to-entry coastal markets and rapidly expanding Sun Belt cities, with a tenant mix focused on essential, necessity-based goods and services that drive multiple shopping trips per week.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?6a387381-bab1-11ed-be0a-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 09:12:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : laxmi.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?6a387457-bab1-11ed-b6b0-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 07:11:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : hafele.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Furniture fittings, architectural hardware, electronic locking systems - Häfele. The hafele.com website is currently being reactivated. On the night of February 2, 2023, there was a ransomware attack on the IT systems of the Häfele Worldwide Group fr...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?6a38752d-bab1-11ed-a36c-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 21:20:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : indigo.ca</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Indigo Books &amp; Music Inc., known as "Indigo" and stylized "!ndigo", is Canada's only major English-language bookstore chain. It is Canada's largest book, gift, and specialty toy retailer, operating stores in all ten provinces and one territory, and t...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?6a387608-bab1-11ed-9054-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 21:10:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : globalcommunities.org</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Global Communities is a global development organization that has grown to reach over 35 countries per year. The non-profit organization was founded in 1952 as the Cooperative Housing Foundation and provided affordable housing for low-income families...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?6a3876de-bab1-11ed-a098-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 13:22:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : cobcreditunion.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>At COB we hold the opinions of every member in the highest regard. Our decisions are truly influenced by the wishes and needs of our members. 300 Million + Borrowed 60 Thousand + Members Explore What COB Has To Offer Let us help you make the best fin...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?6a3877b3-bab1-11ed-9f0d-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 13:22:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : wmich.edu</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Western Michigan University is a public research university in Kalamazoo, Michigan. It was initially established as Western State Normal School in 1903 by Governor Aaron T. Bliss for the training of teachers.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?6a3878a1-bab1-11ed-93f5-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 13:22:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : georgeleslie.co.uk</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>George Leslie is a Civil Engineering Contractor that has operated in Scotland for nearly 60 years. Based in Barrhead, East Renfrewshire, we operate across Scotland and beyond working on Marine projects, Water Management, Infrastructure and Energy.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?6a387978-bab1-11ed-beed-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 13:22:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : df.senac.br</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Senac Distrito Federal - DF Conheça Nossos cursos! Inovação na Prática! revolucione o seu futuro! cursos livres Aprenda com cursos rápidos, práticos e conectados com as inovações do mercado. Acessar cursos Técnicos Cursos práticos e de média duração...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?6a387a4c-bab1-11ed-83e7-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 13:22:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : haeco.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Hong Kong Aircraft Engineering Company Limited is one of the world's leading independent aircraft engineering and maintenance groups with its head office located at Hong Kong International Airport. Established in 1950, the HAECO Group comprises 16 op...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?6a387b21-bab1-11ed-9eef-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 13:22:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : nokair.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Nok Air is a low-cost airline in Thailand operating mostly domestic services out of Bangkok's Don Mueang International Airport. Thai Airways International owns the fourth-largest stake in the airline.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?6a387c09-bab1-11ed-a926-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 13:22:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : princepalace.co.th</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>With six restaurants and bars, Prince Palace Hotel is passionate about serving guests delightful eating and drinking experiences, including at celebrated Cantonese, Japanese, Thai and international restaurants and a scenic pool bar. The two curvaceou...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?6a387cdf-bab1-11ed-8225-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 13:22:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : thinkwelty.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>We are Welty Building Company and we Build to Last. Headquartered in Akron, Ohio and working nationally, Welty has been serving the construction needs of clients throughout Ohio for over 75 years. At Welty we bring an emotional intelligence to our work that is unlike anything else in the construction industry. Our approach is founded on a willingness to defy doing things the way they have always been done in favor of doing what is the smartest, most efficient, most sustainable and ultimately the most beneficial for our customer and the community they serve. We call it “Thinking Welty” and it means we are never afraid to do what is right.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?6a387db5-bab1-11ed-907e-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 11:06:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : INDIKA ENERGY GLOBAL</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Over 15 Indonesian companies were hacked.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?6a387ea0-bab1-11ed-8d18-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 11:06:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Coole Bevis Solicitors</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>At Coole Bevis LLP Solicitors, we understand that life is a journey, with many twists and turns along the way. Our team of specialist solicitors, legal executives, consultants and support staff are right there with you, helping you to navigate the good and bad times. There’s a reason we’re the law firm of choice in Sussex and beyond.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?6a387f7f-bab1-11ed-aff8-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 11:06:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : lsa-international.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>LSA International is one of Europe's leading brands of contemporary handmade glass &amp; high quality porcelain. Shop for Wine glasses, Vases and glassware.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?6a388056-bab1-11ed-b072-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 09:07:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : ilfsindia.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>IL&amp;FS has been registered as a Systemically Important Non-Deposit Accepting Core Investment Company. On October 01, 2018, based on a petition by Union of India, the erstwhile Board of Directors was suspended by the NCLT with immediate effect and New...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?6a388144-bab1-11ed-be3f-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 02:32:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ snatch has just published a now post : Ingenico</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/snatch</link><description>We help you navigate a new world of commerce, in which verticalisation, expanded services, and digital players are transforming the payments landscape. We are the trusted partner of financial institutions, retail chains and small merchants alike, supplying them with simple and reliable payments solutions.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/snatch?6a38821d-bab1-11ed-a676-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 21:08:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ snatch has just published a now post : MSX International</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/snatch</link><description>For more than 25 years, we’ve been a dedicated partner to leading automotive brands around the world. We support them in transforming their businesses and in managing their operations across the areas of Customer Experience, Repair Optimization, Learning and Insights.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/snatch?6a3882f2-bab1-11ed-8959-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 21:08:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : rosenbauer.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>rosenbaueramerica.comRosenbauer is the world's largest producer of custom fire trucks worldwide with 14 factory locations and more than 150 years of experience.rosenbauer\veeam_admin:R%senbau3r2017!administrator@vsphere.local R0s3nb@u3r232GB</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?6a3883c7-bab1-11ed-bbb9-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 13:42:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : hyosung.jp</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>制作の流れについて格安ホームページ制作・システム開発 「孝」</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?6a3884b1-bab1-11ed-b256-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 13:31:20 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>