<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ransomware.live RSS Feed</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/rss.xml</link><description>Last 50 entries monitoring by Ransomware.live</description><image><url>https://www.ransomware.live/ransomwarelive.png</url><title>Ransomware.live RSS Feed</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/rss.xml</link></image><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : kboattorneys.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Organizations, groups of attorneys, and others across the country have recognized KBA’s attorneys in many different ways. Our attorneys are published and are invited to speak at conferences where thousands of attorneys from across America come to lea...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?41364a96-b25a-11ed-9aae-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 23:24:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : treves-group.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Trèves est un groupe industriel spécialisé dans la fourniture d'équipements pour l'industrie automobile.250 GB DATAexample creds ESXIhttps://10.230.1.11/ui/ root:oel28&amp;CPhttps://10.230.1.21/ui/ root:oel28&amp;CPhttps://10.230.1.15/ui/ root:oel2...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?413663e2-b25a-11ed-bc9d-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 23:24:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : beacontech.net</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Since 1999 Beacon Technologies has been a leading partner in the transformation of the Nashville landscape through an integrated process of delivering Telecom, Audio Visual and Life and Safety expertise to the design and development of leading edge c...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?4136658e-b25a-11ed-a431-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 23:24:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : vuu.edu</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Virginia Union UniversityVirginia Union University is a private historically black Baptist university in Richmond, Virginia. It is affiliated with the American Baptist Churches USA.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?413666c6-b25a-11ed-9c21-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 23:12:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : lasegunda.com.ar</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>La Segunda Seguros CLSG is a company that operates in the Insurance industry. It employs 2,001-5,000 people and has $500M-$1B of revenue. The company is headquartered in Rosario, Santa Fe Province, ArgentinaDuring our attack, all the servers of t...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?413667cc-b25a-11ed-90df-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:28:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : lyonhealy.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>From the hallowed halls of the New York Philharmonic to the Bolshoi Ballet, Lyon &amp; Healy Harps is acclaimed throughout the world for its remarkable depth and clarity of sound, breathtaking designs, and rich heritage of quality craftsmanship. With 130...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?413668b8-b25a-11ed-ac09-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 21:16:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ vendetta has just published a now post : Highwealth</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vendetta</link><description>In the best location, build the best house, the best homeMore than 30 years ago, we started our business in Kaohsiung. After laying the foundation, we developed all the way north and expanded to Tainan, Taichung, Hsinchu, Taipei, New...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vendetta?41366997-b25a-11ed-add8-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 15:13:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ play has just published a now post : I???o e???t???</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play</link><description>Germany</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play?41366a78-b25a-11ed-86c7-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 02:44:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lorenz has just published a now post : Hopsteiner</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lorenz</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lorenz?41366b59-b25a-11ed-8e89-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 17:25:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : UNIS</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description>Founded in 1989, Unis LLC has grown into a majority, nationally recognized Third-Party Logistics Provider (3PL). From humble beginnings with just a few trucks operating in Southern California, Unis has expanded into all major US markets, impacting the successful flow of commerce with superior technology, smarter supply chains, and faster execution.We credit our growth to an agile, customer-driven mindset, and strategic investments in technologies that give our clients the visibility and operational insights they require in today’s dynamic supply chain environment</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?41366c48-b25a-11ed-bc8c-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 15:13:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : DALLAS SCHOOL DISTRICT</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description>Dallas School District is centered on students, powered by collaboration, built on equity and driven by excellence.Headquarters: 111 SW Ash St, Dallas, Oregon, 97338, United StatesPhone: (503) 623-5594</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?41366d33-b25a-11ed-a5ee-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 13:33:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : Ancora - Sistemas de Fixacao</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?41366e14-b25a-11ed-9e9f-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 13:32:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ qilin has just published a now post : https://https://gigatron.rs/</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/qilin</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/qilin?41366f07-b25a-11ed-90b1-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 13:30:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : carlocksystems.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Car Lock Systems is dé leverancier van autosleutels en autosloten voor automotive bedrijven.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?41366ff9-b25a-11ed-b14a-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 09:23:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ medusa has just published a now post : International Center of Photography</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa</link><description>New York,  374 Employees. 

The International Center of Photography is the world's leading institution dedicated to photography and visual culture. Cornell Capa founded ICP in 1974 to champion "concerned photography"-socially and politically minded images that can educate and change the world</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa?413670db-b25a-11ed-a92a-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 23:14:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : BakerMechanicalInc.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Baker Mechanical Inc. is a family-oriented company that prides itself on ensuring unsurpassed customer satisfaction.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?413671d0-b25a-11ed-b2d6-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 19:44:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : jetboxcargo.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>El Corporativo JetBox como especialista en el servicio de logística internacional, posee una amplia trayectoria en transporte aéreo y marítimo,con origen en Estados Unidos para Costa Rica. Cuenta con su propia Agencia Aduanal y ofrece los servicios...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?413672aa-b25a-11ed-8839-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 19:44:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : servicesfinanciersjdf.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>JDF Services financiers est un cabinet d'assurances collectives et de personnes spécialisé dans le domaine depuis le début des années 90.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?4136737d-b25a-11ed-84af-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 19:44:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : laremo.de</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Laremo Ihr Spezialist für Landtechnik, Nutzfahrzeuge, Baumaschinen, Fahrzeug- und Umwelttechnik, Stahlbau, Reifencenter, Traktoren, Mähdrescher, CLAAS, IVECO in Thüringen Greiz, Gera, Jena, Erfurt.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?41367470-b25a-11ed-b6fd-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 19:43:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : elliotthomes.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Find your new construction home by Elliott Homes, home builder in Sacramento CA, Phoenix AZ and Yuma AZ. Explore our new home communities today!</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?4136753e-b25a-11ed-9b7a-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 19:39:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : anthonymartin.be</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Anthony Martin encourage une consommation responsable de ses bières. En entrant dans ce site vous reconnaissez avoir l'âge légal pour boire de l'alcoo</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?41367604-b25a-11ed-be13-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 19:26:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Leal Group</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>The Leal Group is a diverse group of companies contributing to the economic development of Mauritius.During the last nine decades, the Leal Group has expanded into a wide range of industries including medical, consumer goods, automotive, information technology, engineering and tourism. The Leal Group is headquartered in Moka, Mauritius.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?413676ca-b25a-11ed-bce5-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 19:24:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : AMADA WELD TECH</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Based in Southern California, AMADA WELD TECH Inc. is a leading manufacturer of equipment and systems for resistance welding, laser welding, laser marking, laser cutting, laser micromachining, and hot bar bonding. Visit our Virtual Showroom!  The company provides products to a wide range of markets, including the medical device, battery, electric vehicle and solar industries, as well as the global electronics, automotive and general industrial markets.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?41367796-b25a-11ed-a63f-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 19:24:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Hengmei Optoelectronics Co.,Ltd.</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Hengmei Optoelectronics Co., Ltd. was established in May 2014, located in Kunshan Development Zone, Jiangsu Province, with a registered capital of 3.25278 billion yuan. At present, four production bases in Kunshan, Fuzhou, Hefei and Danyang have been established and planned, and the total annual production capacity of polarizers is planned to be 220 million square meters. It will become the world's leading polarizer manufacturer and provide high-quality panel factories in many countries and regions around the world. , Stable polarizer supply. Among them, Hengmei Kunshan factory has a total of two polarizer production lines. Line 1 has a width of 1.5M. It was officially mass-produced in January 2017, with a monthly production capacity of 1.8 million square meters. Line 2 has a width of 2.5M and began mass production in September 2019. , with a monthly production capacity of 3.2 million square meters. The two lines have achieved an annual production capacity of 60 million square meters. Hengmei Fuzhou factory has newly added two 2.6M ultra-wide polarizer production lines. It is planned to start mass production in Q4 of 2022. After full production, the two lines will have an annual production capacity of 90 million square meters.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?4136785c-b25a-11ed-9156-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 19:24:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Cansew</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Cansew has been part of the fabric of life since 1924. When it comes time to place your orders, you will find that our more than 80 years of experience and our position as a leading supplier of threads and trim to the needletrade industry will serve your needs exce</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?41367922-b25a-11ed-8fea-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 19:24:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Wawasee Community School Corporation</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>The Wawasee Community School Corporation works to create an academic, social, and physical environment that facilitates growth in each student. They are headquartered in Syracuse, Indiana</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?413679fe-b25a-11ed-a1af-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 19:24:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : SINGLESOURCE</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Single Source is a custom foodservice distribution company providing exceptional logistics management services to our customers, nationwide thru our network of ten distribution centers.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?41367ac2-b25a-11ed-be66-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 19:21:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : championfp.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Founded in Savannah in 1983, Champion Fire Protection has been a market leader in design, fabrication, and installation of fire sprinkler systems.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?41367b87-b25a-11ed-8858-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 17:20:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : sandycove.org</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Sandy Cove's mission is to help you connect with God and each other in order to be transformed into the image of Christ, through His Word</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?41367c4d-b25a-11ed-84c4-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 15:32:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : primorossi.com.br</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Invista em seu sonho de forma planejada. Adquira seu consórcio de forma prática e segura. Confie em quem tem mais de 50 anos de tradição. Saiba mais!</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?41367d15-b25a-11ed-ad60-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 15:32:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : isosteo.fr</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Institut Supérieur d’Ostéopathie Lyon, ISOstéo Lyon a participé activement à la création du 1er enseignement de l’ostéopathie en formation initiale post-bac.Le Diplôme d’Ostéopathie (D.O) délivré par ISOstéo Lyon est reconnu Niveau 7 RNCP et permet...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?41367ddb-b25a-11ed-bffe-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 15:31:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : diavaz.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>The DIAVAZ Group is an organization of companies and strategic alliances created mainly to provide integrated solutions for the oil industry using the most advanced technologies available on the market.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?41367ea4-b25a-11ed-971d-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 15:29:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : aguasdoporto.pt</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Aguas do Porto is a municipal water utility company that manages full water cycle including water supply, wastewater drainage.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?41367f79-b25a-11ed-966a-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 15:26:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : inowai.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Using the human factor as the driving force of excellence and quality as the lever of productivity, INOWAI has established itself as a leader in residential and professional real estate consulting in Luxembourg for more than 20 years.Our goal: to off...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?4136803e-b25a-11ed-a870-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 15:13:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : piercetransit.org</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Pierce Transit is proud to serve our community as Pierce County’s local public transportation service. In 2019 we provided more than 9 million rides to people headed to work, medical appointments, entertainment, grocery shopping, visits with friends...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?41368117-b25a-11ed-bfd0-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 05:32:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ medusa has just published a now post : AP Emissions Technologies</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa</link><description>Automotive Parts · North Carolina, United States

AP® Emissions Technologies is one of the leading manufacturers and suppliers of automotive, light truck, and heavy-duty exhaust and emissions products under the AP®, DuraFit®, Eastern Catalytic®, CATCO ®, ANSA®, Cherry Bomb®, DieselTech™, DuraFit™, Maremont®, XLERA and much more.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa?413681df-b25a-11ed-b960-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 00:23:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : myerspower.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>myerspower.comlabriegroup.commielectric.comaeti.comthese four companies were in the same domain! all their networks were encryptedroot:gear$N0stra*aeti\admin:_NYt7~St]ye'root:$a53ty!myersamerica\tadmin:$a53ty!myerspower:Xiw6zvbp37gx...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?413682ae-b25a-11ed-ad51-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 00:22:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : vissan.com.vn</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>VISSAN Joint Stock Company is one of the leading business corporations in Vietnam. Originally founded on November 20, 1970 and launched on May 18, 1974, VISSAN is proud to become one of the leading nationally recognized food producers.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?4136837a-b25a-11ed-af6f-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 00:22:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : newbridge.org</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Founded in 1963, NewBridge Services is a non-profit organization that provides mental healthcare services to individuals of all ages.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?41368454-b25a-11ed-8493-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 00:22:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : vitrox.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>ViTrox Corporation Berhad (MYX: 0097) is a Malaysian based electronics company located at Penang, Malaysia. Vitrox specializes in designing and developing automated vision inspection system and equipment testers for the semiconductor and electronic p...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?4136852f-b25a-11ed-a4de-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 00:22:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : royallepage.ca</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Since 1913, Royal LePage has been helping Canadians buy and sell their homes and supporting communitiesQuebec City branch</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?413685fa-b25a-11ed-bf6c-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 00:22:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : cordfinancial.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Our Story – ATM ServicesNationwide Provider of Innovative Solutions: ATM Services &amp; ProductsIn 2001, CORD Financial Services was founded by The FIKES Companies. With a small staff and hard work, CORD quickly gained success in central Texas. Throu...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?413686d5-b25a-11ed-a480-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 00:22:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : fikes.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>https://www.fikes.com/COMMERCIAL CLEANING &amp; FACILITY MAINTENANCE SERVICESThere are many moving parts to make sure a business runs successfully, and cleanliness is the most important one. When you are looking for facility maintenance services, you...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?4136879f-b25a-11ed-90f8-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 00:22:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : alliedtools.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Allied International was founded in 1962 as an import distributor of hardware products. Over the years, with our unwavering commitment to innovation, quality, value and service, we have earned the reputation as the recognized market leader in our cor...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?41368863-b25a-11ed-a010-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 00:22:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : hotdesk.me</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Hotdesk.me and their customers such as Barrington James (barringtonjames.com), Sarnac Partners (sarnacpartnertners.com), Hardman &amp; Watson (hardmanandwatson.co.uk), Penspen (penspen.com), Perkins &amp; Will (perkinswill.com), etc.We can't confirm if any...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?4136893a-b25a-11ed-96cd-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 00:22:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : innophaseinc.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>InnoPhase is a fabless semiconductor company that develops innovative and efficient RF architectures using CMOS technology. Building on our previous experience with WLAN IoT products, we have now turned our attention to building energy efficient radi...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?41368a00-b25a-11ed-9310-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 00:22:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ bianlian has just published a now post : NESG</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian</link><description>Group of Osteopathic Physicians who provide surgical health care at its highest level of expertise.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian?41368ac3-b25a-11ed-b21f-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 00:22:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ bianlian has just published a now post : Fibertec</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian</link><description>Fibertec Environmental Services is a full-service environmental analytical laboratory, specializing in subsurface investigations, industrial hygiene, and natural gas analysis.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian?41368b9a-b25a-11ed-b288-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 00:22:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ bianlian has just published a now post : Suburban Laboratories</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian</link><description>Suburban Laboratories was founded in 1936. The original lab was located in Cicero, Illinois where it remained for over 30 years. In 1970 the lab was purchased by three professional engineers; Dr. Fred Gurnham, Robert Konvalinka and Earl Rosenberg.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian?41368c5f-b25a-11ed-9d32-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 00:22:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : Evans Consoles</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description>For over four decades, Evans has been the global leader in providing innovative solutions for mission-critical operations. We serve a diverse client base, including public safety, aviation, process control, utilities, and technology, as well as numerous government agencies. With the industry’s largest portfolio of projects worldwide, serving 15 industries, it’s our proven methodology, strict quality standards, and experience that make the difference for our customers. Looking for current openings? Jump on over to our careers page.Our executive team is the most experienced in the industry and provides the thought leadership that positions Evans as the Global Leader in mission-critical operations, console design and manufacturing.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?41368de8-b25a-11ed-9cdb-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 13:56:47 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>