<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ransomware.live RSS Feed</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/rss.xml</link><description>Last 50 entries monitoring by Ransomware.live</description><image><url>https://www.ransomware.live/ransomwarelive.png</url><title>Ransomware.live RSS Feed</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/rss.xml</link></image><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : globalcommunities.org</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Global Communities is a global development organization that has grown to reach over 35 countries per year. The non-profit organization was founded in 1952 as the Cooperative Housing Foundation and provided affordable housing for low-income families...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?b56c7776-b78b-11ed-90f3-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 13:22:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : cobcreditunion.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>At COB we hold the opinions of every member in the highest regard. Our decisions are truly influenced by the wishes and needs of our members. 300 Million + Borrowed 60 Thousand + Members Explore What COB Has To Offer Let us help you make the best fin...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?b56c9a50-b78b-11ed-b58d-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 13:22:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : wmich.edu</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Western Michigan University is a public research university in Kalamazoo, Michigan. It was initially established as Western State Normal School in 1903 by Governor Aaron T. Bliss for the training of teachers.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?b56c9c99-b78b-11ed-b6b8-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 13:22:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : georgeleslie.co.uk</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>George Leslie is a Civil Engineering Contractor that has operated in Scotland for nearly 60 years. Based in Barrhead, East Renfrewshire, we operate across Scotland and beyond working on Marine projects, Water Management, Infrastructure and Energy.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?b56c9f69-b78b-11ed-bb99-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 13:22:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : df.senac.br</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Senac Distrito Federal - DF Conheça Nossos cursos! Inovação na Prática! revolucione o seu futuro! cursos livres Aprenda com cursos rápidos, práticos e conectados com as inovações do mercado. Acessar cursos Técnicos Cursos práticos e de média duração...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?b56ca1ed-b78b-11ed-af6d-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 13:22:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : haeco.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Hong Kong Aircraft Engineering Company Limited is one of the world's leading independent aircraft engineering and maintenance groups with its head office located at Hong Kong International Airport. Established in 1950, the HAECO Group comprises 16 op...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?b56ca2fa-b78b-11ed-a01c-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 13:22:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : nokair.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Nok Air is a low-cost airline in Thailand operating mostly domestic services out of Bangkok's Don Mueang International Airport. Thai Airways International owns the fourth-largest stake in the airline.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?b56ca3fd-b78b-11ed-ab4d-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 13:22:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : princepalace.co.th</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>With six restaurants and bars, Prince Palace Hotel is passionate about serving guests delightful eating and drinking experiences, including at celebrated Cantonese, Japanese, Thai and international restaurants and a scenic pool bar. The two curvaceou...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?b56ca4f3-b78b-11ed-b5ce-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 13:22:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : thinkwelty.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>We are Welty Building Company and we Build to Last. Headquartered in Akron, Ohio and working nationally, Welty has been serving the construction needs of clients throughout Ohio for over 75 years. At Welty we bring an emotional intelligence to our work that is unlike anything else in the construction industry. Our approach is founded on a willingness to defy doing things the way they have always been done in favor of doing what is the smartest, most efficient, most sustainable and ultimately the most beneficial for our customer and the community they serve. We call it “Thinking Welty” and it means we are never afraid to do what is right.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?b56ca63a-b78b-11ed-8ba2-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 11:06:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : INDIKA ENERGY GLOBAL</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Over 15 Indonesian companies were hacked.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?b56ca81c-b78b-11ed-a1a2-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 11:06:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Coole Bevis Solicitors</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>At Coole Bevis LLP Solicitors, we understand that life is a journey, with many twists and turns along the way. Our team of specialist solicitors, legal executives, consultants and support staff are right there with you, helping you to navigate the good and bad times. There’s a reason we’re the law firm of choice in Sussex and beyond.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?b56ca91f-b78b-11ed-8659-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 11:06:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : lsa-international.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>LSA International is one of Europe's leading brands of contemporary handmade glass &amp; high quality porcelain. Shop for Wine glasses, Vases and glassware.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?b56caab8-b78b-11ed-a491-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 09:07:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : ilfsindia.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>IL&amp;FS has been registered as a Systemically Important Non-Deposit Accepting Core Investment Company. On October 01, 2018, based on a petition by Union of India, the erstwhile Board of Directors was suspended by the NCLT with immediate effect and New...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?b56cabce-b78b-11ed-91a8-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 02:32:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ snatch has just published a now post : Ingenico</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/snatch</link><description>We help you navigate a new world of commerce, in which verticalisation, expanded services, and digital players are transforming the payments landscape. We are the trusted partner of financial institutions, retail chains and small merchants alike, supplying them with simple and reliable payments solutions.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/snatch?b56cacce-b78b-11ed-8749-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 21:08:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ snatch has just published a now post : MSX International</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/snatch</link><description>For more than 25 years, we’ve been a dedicated partner to leading automotive brands around the world. We support them in transforming their businesses and in managing their operations across the areas of Customer Experience, Repair Optimization, Learning and Insights.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/snatch?b56cadc3-b78b-11ed-9912-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 21:08:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : rosenbauer.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>rosenbaueramerica.comRosenbauer is the world's largest producer of custom fire trucks worldwide with 14 factory locations and more than 150 years of experience.rosenbauer\veeam_admin:R%senbau3r2017!administrator@vsphere.local R0s3nb@u3r232GB</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?b56cafa2-b78b-11ed-9bf9-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 13:42:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : hyosung.jp</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>制作の流れについて格安ホームページ制作・システム開発 「孝」</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?b56cb0a8-b78b-11ed-a086-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 13:31:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ vendetta has just published a now post : Chowtaifook</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vendetta</link><description>Chow Tai Fook “Lodestar” CollectionCelebrate a Lustrous Love Story2023-01-26This Valentine's Day, let the “Lodestar” Collection shine upon your journey to everlasting love, commemorated by the traceable T...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vendetta?b56cb30a-b78b-11ed-8505-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 11:26:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : moci.gov.kw</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>The Ministry of Commerce and Industry is responsible for supporting and supervising commercial and economic activities and providing goods, materials and services.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?b56cb4c1-b78b-11ed-bf82-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 11:25:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : wsisd.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>White Settlement Independent School District is a public school district based in White Settlement, Texas. The district serves students in White Settlement and a portion of Fort Worth in west central Tarrant County. In 2009, the school district was r...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?b56cb6b0-b78b-11ed-b1c1-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 11:25:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : bocca-sacs.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Discover the food packaging specialist. Bocca-Sacs offers you paper bags, trays, labeling material and all the necessary food packaging.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?b56cb8b6-b78b-11ed-99fb-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 11:25:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : wcso.us</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Washington County Sheriff’s Office official mobile app.We are committed to not only protecting, but also serving the citizens of Washington County with professionalism, integrity, and transparency. A part of that commitment is to provide you with the...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?b56cba9d-b78b-11ed-b518-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 11:25:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : pcproductsinter.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>P.C. Products International Co., Ltd. is a world leading manufacturer of wheel balancing weight for automotive and aftermarket. We have over 30 years of experience in supplying to major automobile global clients like Ford, Toyota, Honda, Isuzu, Mitsu...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?b56cbbcd-b78b-11ed-9d45-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 11:24:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : carveraero.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Owned by CL Enterprises, Carver Aero(www.carveraero.com)has fixed-base operations in Muscatine and Davenport, Iowa. Carver Aero provides corporate and general aviation services in Iowa, including charter flights, corporate pilot services, airplane ma...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?b56cbda9-b78b-11ed-be18-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 11:12:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : cotteeparker.com.au</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Founded in 1989, Cottee Parker combine intellect and creativity with a skilful, sensitive approach to design. We design considering culture, environment and the human condition to produce responsive and sustainable solutions. We use our experience, s...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?b56cbeb6-b78b-11ed-813a-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 09:15:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ bianlian has just published a now post : G&amp;G Electronics</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian</link><description>G&amp;G Electronics is the store of home appliances and has a great selection of premium brands such as Sony, Bose, Panasonic, Denon, Marantz, Monster, GoPro, Sonos, EcoXGear and more.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian?b56cbfc1-b78b-11ed-9fd1-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 13:30:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ bianlian has just published a now post : A**** ********* ********* &amp; *****</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian</link><description>A firm serving San Antonio, TX in Insurance Defense, Workers Compensation Defense and Civil Trial Practice cases.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian?b56cc167-b78b-11ed-a32d-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 13:30:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ bianlian has just published a now post : D***</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian</link><description>Company that developing a wide range of sophisticated accounting software and electronic commerce applications.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian?b56cc3eb-b78b-11ed-beae-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 13:29:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Smarter Capital</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Smarter Capital is keen to spawn the next generation of technology companies and innovators. Smarter Capital collaborates with executives, mentors, other financial investors and industry particpants to create significant value.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?b56cc590-b78b-11ed-9855-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 07:21:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : ispace.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>iSpace is a leading technology and business process services company serving the healthcare, automotive, entertainment and financial services industries. Founded in 2000, our more than 600 professionals worldwide serve more than 25 Fortune 500 compan...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?b56cc697-b78b-11ed-97a1-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 21:19:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ play has just published a now post : InPro electric</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play</link><description>Germany</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play?b56cc907-b78b-11ed-bf09-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 19:23:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : Schwartz Hautmont Port Shop</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description>Schwartz Hautmont is a private Spanish corporation established in 1963 in Tarragona, South of Barcelona, Spain. The company is in the steel construction business, offering a wide range of products and related services</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?b56cca03-b78b-11ed-b4e0-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 15:12:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : The Keen Group</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>A little about us - The Keen Group provides a professional, licensed, hassle-free minicab &amp; courier service across south London</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?b56ccafb-b78b-11ed-b359-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 11:21:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Glovers Solicitors LLP</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Glovers was founded as Glover &amp; Co in Mayfair in 1932 by Sir Gerald Glover, a prominent and respected Central London property developer and solicitor.  We have since grown to become a modern and highly regarded, property-focused legal practice and are now based in Covent Garden.  Glovers is recognised by clients and independent legal directories as a genuinely partner-led law firm, with in- depth strengths in its chosen practice areas.  Our clients value not only our legal expertise, but also our dedicated work ethic and the commercial approach that we bring to negotiations and problem solving. We are, as a result, retained by a wide range of businesses – from well known restaurant and retail brands and major construction companies to specialist banks and lending institutions.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?b56ccc11-b78b-11ed-8583-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 11:16:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ ransomhouse has just published a now post : AESCULAPIUS Farmaceutici</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/ransomhouse</link><description>The Research and Development Division is the heart of the company, which invests significant resources in innovation to develop new pharmaceutical products and new formulations with high technological content.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/ransomhouse?b56ccdb9-b78b-11ed-8c68-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 07:17:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ mallox has just published a now post : "FICCI"</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/mallox</link><description>Established in 1927, FICCI is the largest and oldest apex business organisation in India. Its history is closely interwoven with India's struggle for independence, its industrialization, and its emergence as one of the most rapidly growing global economies.A non-government, not-for-profit organisation, FICCI is the voice of India's business and industry. From influencing policy to encouraging debate, engaging with policy makers and civil society, FICCI articulates the views and concerns of industry. It serves its members from the Indian private and public corporate sectors and multinational companies, drawing its strength from diverse regional chambers of commerce and industry across states, reaching out to over 2,50,000 companies.FICCI provides a platform for networking and consensus building within and across sectors and is the first port of call for Indian industry, policy makers and the international business community.  FILES: https://anonfiles.com/h9F2u9Z3yc/FICCI_rar PASSWORD: BUHgv97yt9f7fcv7c-p8 </description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/mallox?b56ccf6d-b78b-11ed-ad56-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 07:16:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Empresa Distribuidora de Electricidad del Este, Revenue $633.6M</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Overview: Edeeste is an electricity distribution company. It offers commercial, industrial and business development, installment agreement, power change, circuit and supply status, concurrence consultation, net measurement program, and other services. --- Industries: Appliances, Electrical, and Electronics Manufacturing --- Type: Government Agency Private --- Company size: 1,001-5,000 employees --- Website: http://www.edeeste.com.do --- Locations: Santo Domingo Este, Santo Domingo HQ Dominican Republic Av. San Vicente de Paúl 321 --- Revenue: $633.6M ---------</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?b56cd227-b78b-11ed-81ec-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 05:29:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : Stone and Electrical Contractors</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description>Stone &amp; Sons Electrical Contractors, Inc offers a wide range of electrical services in the Transportation, Industrial and Municipal Markets including new construction, custom designs/installations, repairs, maintenance and systems upgrades.﻿First established in 1994, our business now has more than 85 field employees as well as a large support staff. Our support staff includes a team of project managers, estimators, and electrical engineers. Together, our team offers our clients over 160 years of combined experience.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?b56cd351-b78b-11ed-8c09-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 23:14:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ ransomhouse has just published a now post : Bond It</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/ransomhouse</link><description>For almost two decades, Bond It has been a manufacturer of high performance, high quality building chemicals such as sealants, adhesives, grouts, cleaners, expanding foams, fillers, decorating sundries, landscaping products and other similar products.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/ransomhouse?b56cd515-b78b-11ed-94db-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 23:13:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : PRESTIGE MAINTENANCE USA WAS HACKED</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Who is Prestige Maintenance USA  Prestige Maintenance USA, established in 1976 and headquartered in Plano, Texas, provides janitorial services that offer contract and project cleaning, general maintenance, window washing, carpet care, sanitation, and recycling services  Headquarters: 1808 10th St Ste 300, Plano, Texas, 75074, United States Phone Number: (972) 578-9801 Revenue: $472.4M Linkedin: http://www.linkedin.com/company/prestige-maintenance-usa Facebook: http://www.facebook.com/pmusa76 Twitter: http://www.twitter.com/prestige_m_usa</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?b56cd847-b78b-11ed-8f7f-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 23:13:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Kendall Hunt Publishing</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Founded in 1944, Kendall Hunt Publishing is a publisher of hands-on, inquiry-based science, mathematics, and gifted curricula for grades PreK-12. Their research and standards-based programs are available in both print and digital components that encompass students</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?b56cdb91-b78b-11ed-9f27-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 23:11:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ medusa has just published a now post : Moose, Martin, Haynes &amp; Lundy</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa</link><description>For years, Moose, Martin, Haynes &amp; Lundy, P.A. has been providing quality, personalized financial guidance to local individuals and businesses. Our expertise ranges from basic tax management and accounting services to more in-depth services such as audits, financia</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa?b56cdcb6-b78b-11ed-ba91-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 21:14:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ ransomexx has just published a now post : BULOG</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/ransomexx</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/ransomexx?b56ce03d-b78b-11ed-bf81-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 19:39:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ ragnarlocker has just published a now post : AASP claim there was no data leakage!</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/ragnarlocker</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/ragnarlocker?b56ce252-b78b-11ed-b21d-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 19:38:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ medusa has just published a now post : RAYAB Consulting Engineers</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa</link><description>RAYAB Consulting Engineers Company was founded in 1984. Taking advantage of hundreds of experienced experts’ cooperation , know – how and scientific experiences, the company has studied , designed and supervised, water and water transmission infrastructural projects, consulting and studying services for potable, agricultural and industrial water consumption, urban and industrial water distribution and wastewater collecting and disposal networks, water and wastewater treatment plants, environmental and health services and water resources conservation as large and small projects throughout Iran In addition to offices in Tehran, it has offices in Isfahan , Ghazvin, Takestan, Gorgan, Karaj, Ghom, Kashan, Delijan, Malayer , Ilaam , Ahwaz, Dezful, Babolsar, Bojnourd, Mashhad, Esfarayen, Kashmar, Birjand, Bandarabbas, Sirjan and Sare – Pole – Zahab</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa?b56ce447-b78b-11ed-b2d2-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 19:37:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : ziapueblo.org</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>The Pueblo of Zia has operated a contemporary court since 2007. It is a court of general jurisdiction and oversees criminal and civil hearings. Currently the Court staff consists of a Chief Judge (part-time), a court clerk and a part time probation o...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?b56ce591-b78b-11ed-ad01-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 19:25:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : nougat-carlier.be</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>For more than half a century, Carlier, a family business, has been making nougat by using the highest quality ingredients, in a wide variety of flavours. It all began in 1949: following the example of his father, a retail confectioner, Rodolphe Carli...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?b56ce795-b78b-11ed-be7a-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 15:26:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : siqueiracastro.com.br</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>stolen 470gb data - finance, acc, reports, contractsActing on all fronts of the business, the so-called full service , is what is expected of a contemporary law firm. We, at SiqueiraCastro, go further. We are pioneers in full solution . With high...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?b56ce8f2-b78b-11ed-b243-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 15:13:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : skylinetrisource.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Find the right fit for your brand with Skyline Trisource Exhibits and Environments in Cleveland. We create custom exhibits, without the custom price tag. Our high-impact graphics, modular structures and comprehensive services make great exhibit desig...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?b56cea1c-b78b-11ed-a3c0-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 13:48:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : fosterfarms.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Change the negotiator.He's obstructing the deal and denying the facts and the obvious obvious. And doesn't want to use valid insurance!Here are scans of insurance documents from the network of companies:http://lockbitfile2tcudkcqqt2ve6btssyvqwl...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?b56cecd8-b78b-11ed-b07f-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 13:37:05 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>