<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ransomware.live RSS Feed</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/rss.xml</link><description>Last 50 entries monitoring by Ransomware.live</description><image><url>https://www.ransomware.live/ransomwarelive.png</url><title>Ransomware.live RSS Feed</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/rss.xml</link></image><item><title>🏴‍☠️ vicesociety has just published a now post : Vesuvius</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety</link><description>Vesuvius provides engineering services and solutions principally to steel and foundry industries worldwide. With 17 research centres across the globe and an annual investment of 33.2 million in research and development, Vesuvius continues to lead innovation in our industry.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety?c0d9a259-b821-11ed-8b83-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 11:10:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : tjel.net</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>AboutUs: Thai Jurong Engineering Limited (TJEL) was incorporated in December 1988. The company's core business is to provide engineering and construction services in the power generation sector. It also undertakes plant erection for industrial plant...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?c0d9bc29-b821-11ed-83ad-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 11:09:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ medusa has just published a now post : Kenya Airports Authority</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa</link><description>Kenya Airports Authority (KAA) is the owner and operator of nine civilian airports and airstrips in Kenya. Kenya Airports Authority was established by an act of Parliament in 1992, by the ruling Kenya African National Union government. The KAA Act, Cap 395, provides for the powers and functions of the Authority. Its head office is on the property of Jomo Kenyatta International Airport in Embakasi, Nairobi.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa?c0d9bdf1-b821-11ed-be42-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 09:13:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : hico-ics.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>HiCo-ICS has been a leading global provider of enterprise IT-solutions for industry, authorities and communities since 1997. HiCo-ICS provides process and system integration, information networking of technical logistic documentation and product info...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?c0d9bf23-b821-11ed-847d-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 09:13:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : egas.no</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?c0d9c031-b821-11ed-ab68-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 09:13:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Kimko Realty</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Kimco Realty® (NYSE:KIM) is a real estate investment trust (REIT) headquartered in Jericho, N.Y. that is North America’s largest publicly traded owner and operator of open-air, grocery-anchored shopping centers, and a growing portfolio of mixed-use assets. The company’s portfolio is primarily concentrated in the first-ring suburbs of the top major metropolitan markets, including those in high-barrier-to-entry coastal markets and rapidly expanding Sun Belt cities, with a tenant mix focused on essential, necessity-based goods and services that drive multiple shopping trips per week.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?c0d9c129-b821-11ed-b787-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 09:12:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : laxmi.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?c0d9c231-b821-11ed-b123-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 07:11:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : hafele.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Furniture fittings, architectural hardware, electronic locking systems - Häfele. The hafele.com website is currently being reactivated. On the night of February 2, 2023, there was a ransomware attack on the IT systems of the Häfele Worldwide Group fr...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?c0d9c317-b821-11ed-980d-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 21:20:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : indigo.ca</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Indigo Books &amp; Music Inc., known as "Indigo" and stylized "!ndigo", is Canada's only major English-language bookstore chain. It is Canada's largest book, gift, and specialty toy retailer, operating stores in all ten provinces and one territory, and t...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?c0d9c3fc-b821-11ed-9216-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 21:10:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : globalcommunities.org</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Global Communities is a global development organization that has grown to reach over 35 countries per year. The non-profit organization was founded in 1952 as the Cooperative Housing Foundation and provided affordable housing for low-income families...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?c0d9c4e1-b821-11ed-b67f-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 13:22:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : cobcreditunion.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>At COB we hold the opinions of every member in the highest regard. Our decisions are truly influenced by the wishes and needs of our members. 300 Million + Borrowed 60 Thousand + Members Explore What COB Has To Offer Let us help you make the best fin...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?c0d9c5e0-b821-11ed-bf48-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 13:22:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : wmich.edu</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Western Michigan University is a public research university in Kalamazoo, Michigan. It was initially established as Western State Normal School in 1903 by Governor Aaron T. Bliss for the training of teachers.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?c0d9c6c0-b821-11ed-af86-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 13:22:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : georgeleslie.co.uk</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>George Leslie is a Civil Engineering Contractor that has operated in Scotland for nearly 60 years. Based in Barrhead, East Renfrewshire, we operate across Scotland and beyond working on Marine projects, Water Management, Infrastructure and Energy.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?c0d9c7ba-b821-11ed-862b-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 13:22:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : df.senac.br</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Senac Distrito Federal - DF Conheça Nossos cursos! Inovação na Prática! revolucione o seu futuro! cursos livres Aprenda com cursos rápidos, práticos e conectados com as inovações do mercado. Acessar cursos Técnicos Cursos práticos e de média duração...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?c0d9c8b1-b821-11ed-904e-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 13:22:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : haeco.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Hong Kong Aircraft Engineering Company Limited is one of the world's leading independent aircraft engineering and maintenance groups with its head office located at Hong Kong International Airport. Established in 1950, the HAECO Group comprises 16 op...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?c0d9c992-b821-11ed-bce7-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 13:22:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : nokair.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Nok Air is a low-cost airline in Thailand operating mostly domestic services out of Bangkok's Don Mueang International Airport. Thai Airways International owns the fourth-largest stake in the airline.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?c0d9ca82-b821-11ed-a1a7-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 13:22:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : princepalace.co.th</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>With six restaurants and bars, Prince Palace Hotel is passionate about serving guests delightful eating and drinking experiences, including at celebrated Cantonese, Japanese, Thai and international restaurants and a scenic pool bar. The two curvaceou...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?c0d9cb5d-b821-11ed-ab1f-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 13:22:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : thinkwelty.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>We are Welty Building Company and we Build to Last. Headquartered in Akron, Ohio and working nationally, Welty has been serving the construction needs of clients throughout Ohio for over 75 years. At Welty we bring an emotional intelligence to our work that is unlike anything else in the construction industry. Our approach is founded on a willingness to defy doing things the way they have always been done in favor of doing what is the smartest, most efficient, most sustainable and ultimately the most beneficial for our customer and the community they serve. We call it “Thinking Welty” and it means we are never afraid to do what is right.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?c0d9cc35-b821-11ed-a78a-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 11:06:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : INDIKA ENERGY GLOBAL</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Over 15 Indonesian companies were hacked.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?c0d9cd2b-b821-11ed-83ce-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 11:06:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Coole Bevis Solicitors</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>At Coole Bevis LLP Solicitors, we understand that life is a journey, with many twists and turns along the way. Our team of specialist solicitors, legal executives, consultants and support staff are right there with you, helping you to navigate the good and bad times. There’s a reason we’re the law firm of choice in Sussex and beyond.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?c0d9ce0d-b821-11ed-b39c-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 11:06:14 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : lsa-international.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>LSA International is one of Europe's leading brands of contemporary handmade glass &amp; high quality porcelain. Shop for Wine glasses, Vases and glassware.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?c0d9cf01-b821-11ed-9dac-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 09:07:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : ilfsindia.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>IL&amp;FS has been registered as a Systemically Important Non-Deposit Accepting Core Investment Company. On October 01, 2018, based on a petition by Union of India, the erstwhile Board of Directors was suspended by the NCLT with immediate effect and New...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?c0d9cfe4-b821-11ed-b679-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 02:32:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ snatch has just published a now post : Ingenico</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/snatch</link><description>We help you navigate a new world of commerce, in which verticalisation, expanded services, and digital players are transforming the payments landscape. We are the trusted partner of financial institutions, retail chains and small merchants alike, supplying them with simple and reliable payments solutions.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/snatch?c0d9d0c0-b821-11ed-a51a-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 21:08:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ snatch has just published a now post : MSX International</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/snatch</link><description>For more than 25 years, we’ve been a dedicated partner to leading automotive brands around the world. We support them in transforming their businesses and in managing their operations across the areas of Customer Experience, Repair Optimization, Learning and Insights.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/snatch?c0d9d19b-b821-11ed-81a3-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 21:08:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : rosenbauer.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>rosenbaueramerica.comRosenbauer is the world's largest producer of custom fire trucks worldwide with 14 factory locations and more than 150 years of experience.rosenbauer\veeam_admin:R%senbau3r2017!administrator@vsphere.local R0s3nb@u3r232GB</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?c0d9d278-b821-11ed-bba1-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 13:42:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : hyosung.jp</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>制作の流れについて格安ホームページ制作・システム開発 「孝」</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?c0d9d352-b821-11ed-91ba-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 13:31:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ vendetta has just published a now post : Chowtaifook</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vendetta</link><description>Chow Tai Fook “Lodestar” CollectionCelebrate a Lustrous Love Story2023-01-26This Valentine's Day, let the “Lodestar” Collection shine upon your journey to everlasting love, commemorated by the traceable T...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vendetta?c0d9d42e-b821-11ed-b758-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 11:26:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : moci.gov.kw</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>The Ministry of Commerce and Industry is responsible for supporting and supervising commercial and economic activities and providing goods, materials and services.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?c0d9d507-b821-11ed-8b91-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 11:25:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : wsisd.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>White Settlement Independent School District is a public school district based in White Settlement, Texas. The district serves students in White Settlement and a portion of Fort Worth in west central Tarrant County. In 2009, the school district was r...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?c0d9d5fb-b821-11ed-abd5-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 11:25:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : bocca-sacs.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Discover the food packaging specialist. Bocca-Sacs offers you paper bags, trays, labeling material and all the necessary food packaging.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?c0d9d6d4-b821-11ed-8a6d-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 11:25:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : wcso.us</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Washington County Sheriff’s Office official mobile app.We are committed to not only protecting, but also serving the citizens of Washington County with professionalism, integrity, and transparency. A part of that commitment is to provide you with the...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?c0d9d7ae-b821-11ed-9715-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 11:25:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : pcproductsinter.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>P.C. Products International Co., Ltd. is a world leading manufacturer of wheel balancing weight for automotive and aftermarket. We have over 30 years of experience in supplying to major automobile global clients like Ford, Toyota, Honda, Isuzu, Mitsu...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?c0d9d8b2-b821-11ed-8e17-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 11:24:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : carveraero.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Owned by CL Enterprises, Carver Aero(www.carveraero.com)has fixed-base operations in Muscatine and Davenport, Iowa. Carver Aero provides corporate and general aviation services in Iowa, including charter flights, corporate pilot services, airplane ma...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?c0d9d991-b821-11ed-9d71-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 11:12:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : cotteeparker.com.au</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Founded in 1989, Cottee Parker combine intellect and creativity with a skilful, sensitive approach to design. We design considering culture, environment and the human condition to produce responsive and sustainable solutions. We use our experience, s...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?c0d9da69-b821-11ed-925c-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 09:15:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ bianlian has just published a now post : G&amp;G Electronics</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian</link><description>G&amp;G Electronics is the store of home appliances and has a great selection of premium brands such as Sony, Bose, Panasonic, Denon, Marantz, Monster, GoPro, Sonos, EcoXGear and more.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian?c0d9db43-b821-11ed-a21d-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 13:30:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ bianlian has just published a now post : A**** ********* ********* &amp; *****</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian</link><description>A firm serving San Antonio, TX in Insurance Defense, Workers Compensation Defense and Civil Trial Practice cases.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian?c0d9dc35-b821-11ed-aaee-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 13:30:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ bianlian has just published a now post : D***</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian</link><description>Company that developing a wide range of sophisticated accounting software and electronic commerce applications.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian?c0d9dd16-b821-11ed-a101-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 13:29:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Smarter Capital</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Smarter Capital is keen to spawn the next generation of technology companies and innovators. Smarter Capital collaborates with executives, mentors, other financial investors and industry particpants to create significant value.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?c0d9de02-b821-11ed-a214-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 Feb 2023 07:21:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : ispace.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>iSpace is a leading technology and business process services company serving the healthcare, automotive, entertainment and financial services industries. Founded in 2000, our more than 600 professionals worldwide serve more than 25 Fortune 500 compan...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?c0d9dedd-b821-11ed-9af9-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 21:19:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ play has just published a now post : InPro electric</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play</link><description>Germany</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play?c0d9dfb6-b821-11ed-8472-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 19:23:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : Schwartz Hautmont Port Shop</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description>Schwartz Hautmont is a private Spanish corporation established in 1963 in Tarragona, South of Barcelona, Spain. The company is in the steel construction business, offering a wide range of products and related services</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?c0d9e0a8-b821-11ed-9b84-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 15:12:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : The Keen Group</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>A little about us - The Keen Group provides a professional, licensed, hassle-free minicab &amp; courier service across south London</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?c0d9e184-b821-11ed-bfd6-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 11:21:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Glovers Solicitors LLP</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Glovers was founded as Glover &amp; Co in Mayfair in 1932 by Sir Gerald Glover, a prominent and respected Central London property developer and solicitor.  We have since grown to become a modern and highly regarded, property-focused legal practice and are now based in Covent Garden.  Glovers is recognised by clients and independent legal directories as a genuinely partner-led law firm, with in- depth strengths in its chosen practice areas.  Our clients value not only our legal expertise, but also our dedicated work ethic and the commercial approach that we bring to negotiations and problem solving. We are, as a result, retained by a wide range of businesses – from well known restaurant and retail brands and major construction companies to specialist banks and lending institutions.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?c0d9e274-b821-11ed-ae86-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 11:16:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ ransomhouse has just published a now post : AESCULAPIUS Farmaceutici</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/ransomhouse</link><description>The Research and Development Division is the heart of the company, which invests significant resources in innovation to develop new pharmaceutical products and new formulations with high technological content.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/ransomhouse?c0d9e378-b821-11ed-a0dc-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 07:17:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ mallox has just published a now post : "FICCI"</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/mallox</link><description>Established in 1927, FICCI is the largest and oldest apex business organisation in India. Its history is closely interwoven with India's struggle for independence, its industrialization, and its emergence as one of the most rapidly growing global economies.A non-government, not-for-profit organisation, FICCI is the voice of India's business and industry. From influencing policy to encouraging debate, engaging with policy makers and civil society, FICCI articulates the views and concerns of industry. It serves its members from the Indian private and public corporate sectors and multinational companies, drawing its strength from diverse regional chambers of commerce and industry across states, reaching out to over 2,50,000 companies.FICCI provides a platform for networking and consensus building within and across sectors and is the first port of call for Indian industry, policy makers and the international business community.  FILES: https://anonfiles.com/h9F2u9Z3yc/FICCI_rar PASSWORD: BUHgv97yt9f7fcv7c-p8 </description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/mallox?c0d9e46b-b821-11ed-bbf9-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 07:16:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Empresa Distribuidora de Electricidad del Este, Revenue $633.6M</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Overview: Edeeste is an electricity distribution company. It offers commercial, industrial and business development, installment agreement, power change, circuit and supply status, concurrence consultation, net measurement program, and other services. --- Industries: Appliances, Electrical, and Electronics Manufacturing --- Type: Government Agency Private --- Company size: 1,001-5,000 employees --- Website: http://www.edeeste.com.do --- Locations: Santo Domingo Este, Santo Domingo HQ Dominican Republic Av. San Vicente de Paúl 321 --- Revenue: $633.6M ---------</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?c0d9e54c-b821-11ed-863e-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 05:29:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : Stone and Electrical Contractors</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description>Stone &amp; Sons Electrical Contractors, Inc offers a wide range of electrical services in the Transportation, Industrial and Municipal Markets including new construction, custom designs/installations, repairs, maintenance and systems upgrades.﻿First established in 1994, our business now has more than 85 field employees as well as a large support staff. Our support staff includes a team of project managers, estimators, and electrical engineers. Together, our team offers our clients over 160 years of combined experience.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?c0d9e627-b821-11ed-982e-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 23:14:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ ransomhouse has just published a now post : Bond It</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/ransomhouse</link><description>For almost two decades, Bond It has been a manufacturer of high performance, high quality building chemicals such as sealants, adhesives, grouts, cleaners, expanding foams, fillers, decorating sundries, landscaping products and other similar products.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/ransomhouse?c0d9e718-b821-11ed-850a-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 23:13:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : PRESTIGE MAINTENANCE USA WAS HACKED</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Who is Prestige Maintenance USA  Prestige Maintenance USA, established in 1976 and headquartered in Plano, Texas, provides janitorial services that offer contract and project cleaning, general maintenance, window washing, carpet care, sanitation, and recycling services  Headquarters: 1808 10th St Ste 300, Plano, Texas, 75074, United States Phone Number: (972) 578-9801 Revenue: $472.4M Linkedin: http://www.linkedin.com/company/prestige-maintenance-usa Facebook: http://www.facebook.com/pmusa76 Twitter: http://www.twitter.com/prestige_m_usa</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?c0d9e7f8-b821-11ed-82ff-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 23:13:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Kendall Hunt Publishing</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Founded in 1944, Kendall Hunt Publishing is a publisher of hands-on, inquiry-based science, mathematics, and gifted curricula for grades PreK-12. Their research and standards-based programs are available in both print and digital components that encompass students</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?c0d9e8d6-b821-11ed-90d5-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Feb 2023 23:11:10 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>